# OLHOROD

## JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# CONTACT



Portfolio website



annapolhorodnyk@gmail.com



Europe



**in** polllyann

# SKILLS

#### **PROFESSIONAL**

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS
- Netlify
- Git
- GitHub
- API
- Bootstrap
- Figma

## EDUCATION

Kyiv Academy of Fine Arts and Architecture 2015 - 2018

SheCodes 4 courses 2022

# PROFILE

Junior front-end developer with a background in development, e-commerce and art. SheCodes front-end development certification. Over 3 years of experience in e-commerce. Passionate about design and always try to find a best and creative way to solve any issue.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Self-employed | June 2022 - present

During this time, I've designed and developed a few websites and weather application using developers' practices and techniques.

- Weather app. Built with: HTML5 / CSS / JavaScript / Bootstrap / API / Netlify
- Portfolio. Built with HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap / Netlify
- Drawing page. Built with HTML5 / CSS / Netlify

#### PRODUCT DATA SPECIALIST

LoveCrafts | Feb 2019 - Present

I gained a lot of knowledge about different systems such as Magento, INRiver PIM, Microsoft Dynamics NAV, Prismic, and Amplitude. I've learned to troubleshoot and how manage vast amounts of information in a better and more creative way. I've designed a data model for 3000 products and was leading a QA project for a while.

# SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING SPECIALIST

Reclamare Digital Agency | Jul 2018 – Nov 2018

I've created tons of images in Photoshop and wrote the same amount of selling and engaging texts for customers from different work areas. I've learned there how marketing should work and how to showcase the most important thoughts through one small post in social media.

#### WRITER

ArtUkraine | Jul 2018 - Nov 2018

It was a very short but productive time working as a freelance writer for Ukrainian art magazine. I visited a few art exhibitions, did some photography and researches and made interviews with different artists. I've wrote 3 articles about old and modern art exhibitions that were held in Kyiv in 2016. You can read them here.